const STORE = [
		{
			question: 'What does the boggart change into when it first sees Neville?',
			answers: [
			'His grandmother',
			'A giant spider',
			'A werewolf',
			'Professor Snape'
			],
			correctAnswer: 'Professor Snape'

		},

		{
			question: 'What kind of dessert does Harry eat at the zoo in Sorcerer\'s Stone',
			answers: [
			'lemon ice pop',
			'ice cream cone',
			'funnel cake',
			'chocolate chip cookie'
			],
			correctAnswer: 'lemon ice pop'
		},

		{
			question: 'How did the Dursleys explain Harry\'s parents\' deaths?',
			answers: [
			'Gas explosion',
			'Car crash',
			'Murder',
			'Train wreck'
			],
			correctAnswer: 'Car crash'
		},

		{
			question: 'In which book does Harry first enter the Hogwarts kitchens?',
			answers: [
			'Book 4 - Goblet of Fire',
			'Book 1 - Sorcerer\'s Stone',
			'Book 6 - Half-blood Prince',
			'Book 7 - Deathly Hallows'
			],
			correctAnswer: 'Book 4 - Goblet of Fire'
		},

		{
			question: 'How many times does Gryffindor win the Quidditch cup while Harry is at Hogwarts?',
			answers: [
			'Once',
			'Twice',
			'Thrice',
			'Six Times'
			],
			correctAnswer: 'Thrice'
		},

		{
			question: 'Which of the following was never the master of the Elder Wand?',
			answers: [
			'Harry Potter',
			'Voldemort',
			'Draco Malfoy',
			'Albus Dumbledore'
			],
			correctAnswer: 'Voldemort'
		},

		{
			question: 'How many teacups did Neville break in his first Divination lesson?',
			answers: [
			'One',
			'Two',
			'Three',
			'Four'
			],
			correctAnswer: 'Two'
		},

		{
			question: 'How much money does Harry win as the Tri-Wizard Tournament champion?',
			answers: [
			'500 pounds',
			'1000 galleons',
			'1500 galleons',
			'500 galleons'
			],
			correctAnswer: '1000 galleons'
		},

		{
			question: 'How old were James and Lilly Potter when they were killed?',
			answers: [
			'33 years old',
			'27 years old',
			'23 years old',
			'21 years old'
			],
			correctAnswer: '21 years old'
		},

		{
			question: 'Who shattered the prophecy in the Department of Mysteries',
			answers: [
			'Lucius Malfoy',
			'Bellatrix Lestrange',
			'Sirius Black',
			'Neville Longbottom'
			],
			correctAnswer: 'Neville Longbottom'
		},
];